(What a Happy Occasion)
- Nice to see you all. - My gosh.
- Congratulations are in order. - Yes.
(Congratulations)
- Is it someone's birthday? - What are we celebrating?
- Our summer retreat episode... - Yes.
aired last week,
and our ratings were through the roof.
We got good ratings.
As for Ji Hyeon's team, Team Cooling Cooling,
people wanted to see them on "Show! Music Core."
- Really? - Yes.
- There were so many comments. - Really?
I'd love that.
(Chuckling)
- You sound like a grandpa. - That sounds amazing.
There's one more thing for us to celebrate.
It's the first for Moosquiat.
You know the design I drew with the tablet PC for the T-shirts?
(A group T-shirt to celebrate the summer retreat)
T-shirts were sold out!
- You can't buy it... - Sold out?
- even if you want to now. - Gosh.
Was it a limited edition?
I was going to buy 100 shirts if no one bought them.
- Okay. - Gosh.
- I couldn't even buy them. - Gosh, what a surprise.
(Laughing)
(The Class of the Real Deal)
"The Class of the Real Deal?"
The Real Deal?
(Art tools are scattered about.)
It's an atelier.
These tools look cool for some reason.
(What are you doing?)
(Painting)
It's a new piece.
(Kian84 is working on his artwork.)
- He's the coolest when he paints. - Exactly.
I've been working on my art.
What's going on?
(Someone has come to his atelier.)
- Sir. - "Sir?"
Sir.
MINHO.
(MINHO is visiting his atelier.)
- You took MINHO. - MINHO?
- I can't believe you're here. - Thank you for inviting me.
Gosh, don't do that.
He was on my team at the summer retreat.
I brought kimchi to the retreat...
and kimchi fried rice on the field day.
I got the feeling that he was looking out for me.
Right. He took good care of you.
(Everyone was horrified by his kimchi fried rice.)
(But I'm more curious about your effort than the taste.)
That was almost a year ago.
He still remembers that touching moment.
(At the summer retreat, he brought plain cabbage kimchi.)
(A series of compliments)
He didn't compliment my anchovies.
He's looking out for me.
(He's grateful to MINHO and his attention.)
(You're okay, right?)
(It's okay, Kian84.)
(It's okay that we lost.)
(We still played better, though.)
Thanks to people like him,
school dropouts...
- keep going. - What are you talking about?
(He gives people courage, so they don't give up.)
He could be the head of a department.
But if he stops looking out for you,
things easily get sour.
Thanks to him, Kian84 didn't drop out.
(I'll do better, MINHO.)
I've always known that he likes to work out.
Deep down, I felt like there was a connection between us.
It thought it would be nice for us to pick a day and hang out.
So I invited him to my atelier.
Sir.
- I can't believe you're here. - Thank you for inviting me.
Gosh, don't do that.
(Impressed)
It doesn't look that good.
(Shy)
- This is amazing. - Gosh, don't say that.
(Kian84 is working on a huge piece.)
The colors look just beautiful.
Right.
This is ruined. I need to fix it.
How is this ruined?
My gosh.
- It looks amazing. - Really?
Yes.
- It looks unrefined. - What?
Gosh, stop it.
- How does it look unrefined? - It just does.
I was going to flip it around because I was too shy.
- You'd never do that. - Since he came...
Stop lying.
I think you brought that from storage.
- That wasn't there before. - Right.
- Stop talking nonsense. - Well...
No. It's not a finished piece, so I was shy to show it.
But I left it in the open.
What do you mean it looks unrefined?
(Bombarding him with compliments as soon as he comes in)
- Well... - Okay.
(Raised cheeks)
(Laughing)
He's shy, but we have to compliment him.
He likes that.
(He's secretly enjoying the compliments.)
It didn't feel right to come here empty-handed.
- You invited me to your atelier. - Okay.
- I brought a present. - You didn't have to.
- My goodness. - He's got a big heart.
- It's a recent hobby of mine. - Okay.
I practiced bonsai a few times.
(Amazed)
- I... - This looks...
repotted my plant into this one.
Isn't it beautiful?
I wanted to give this to you as a present.
- Hey. - It's a new hobby of mine.
Before that, my only hobby was working out.
I thought I should try an activity...
- that required me to be still. - Right.
I recently tried it out.
- And I actually liked it. - Right.
I did think that it would be nice...
for him to do a calming activity.
- I bought a plant, - Okay.
- so I could give it to you. - You made this?
- I repotted it... - Okay.
and trimmed it.
You made it yourself?
I also put moss on it myself.
I thought this would make a nice present.
- It looks beautiful. - Right.
I always thought this looked cool.
- Take good care of it. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- It looks great. - Right.
Will this piece go to an exhibit?
I have to.
The moment I walked in,
- I was overwhelmed by it. - Gosh.
It instantly drew me in. I mean it.
Kian84 must look different in there.
It's more fascinating once it's on display at an exhibit.
You're making me shy.
(His cheeks are raised once again.)
He likes that.
Talking about this is making me shy.
- Why? - I'm shy!
(I'm shy!)
You can't look him in the face.
He kept complimenting me. I felt awkward.
Wait.
- It's 1pm. - It's 1pm?
- Should we get going? - Right.
Go where?
Anyway, don't kill the plant.
- I won't. - Okay.
- I'll take it home. - Okay.
Gosh, you startled me. I thought you were getting naked.
I thought you weren't wearing anything underneath.
My gosh. Hey.
- Here. - Put it in here.
My gosh.
- Hey, did it cost a lot of money? - No, it didn't.
Let's go.
(Kian84 and MINHO go out.)
Where are they going?
I hope it doesn't rain.
It's been raining quite frequently lately.
Let's take my car.
Let's go.
My gosh.
(They quickly get into his car.)
What a cute car.
- Let's get going. - Okay.
(Glancing back)
Gosh, there's only workout-related stuff in your car.
I've never seen a wall ball in someone's car.
Is this a car for a pro athlete?
(It looks like an athlete's car.)
(Setting out with his workout gear)
(Rustling)
- As long as we can do that... - Okay.
- What's he doing? - What is he applying to his hair?
Let me fix my hair.
(Your hair?)
I can do it with three ice cubes.
Wait.
- With the ice cubes from coffee? - Yes.
Like beads.
(Americano Hair)
(He's washing his face while he's at it.)
I always...
- He suddenly took them out. - With the ice from coffee?
I usually fix my hair with water.
But I didn't have water, so I used the ice cubes.
(Laughing)
At the Blue Dragon Film Awards,
they did a handprint event.
Like some old guys at a rib restaurant,
he used the wet towel to wipe his face.
(At the Blue Dragon Film Awards,)
(the camera was panning across...)
(Stopping)
(He didn't let it stop him and kept wiping his face.)
("Kian84 Flusters Everyone with His Unexpected Action")
- I wasn't going to do that. - You weren't?
- Did you not wash your face? - I just can't help myself.
You can't help yourself around wet towels?
I have to do it.
I had to style my hair and all.
It's nice that the coffee didn't go to waste.
(Clean84)
I always try to look neat.
Do you really style your hair with ice?
No. I don't have water here.
- He was styling himself. - I was styling myself.
- Wait. You look neat now. - So...
I look super neat afterward.
Gosh, my hair smells like Americano.
Exactly. I mean...
Seriously. I'm an odd one, aren't I?
(The savory aroma of coffee fills the car.)
You're definitely one of a kind.
Gosh, look at the weather.
Actually, some rain would be nice.
Right. I want it to pour down...
instead of drizzling like this.
I like running in the rain.
- Running in the rain is fun. - Yes.
- I like it. - What's your record for 10km?
- What was your 1st record? - My 1st record was 45 minutes.
- Your 1st record? - Yes. It was my 1st record.
I can't believe you finished your 1st 10km run in 45 minutes.
I want to help you get your PB.
- Mine? - Yes.
- Help me then. - So...
- What's PB? - Personal Best.
Your personal best record.
They're going to a mountain.
Are you guys hiking today?
- We're here. - Thank you for driving us.
(They arrive at the mountain-looking destination.)
I hope it doesn't rain.
Gosh, he set up his own here.
- There. - I see tents over there.
(Kian84 and MINHO spot something.)
- Na Ra. - Na Ra.
- Na Ra? - It's Na Ra.
- Hey. - Wait.
- You're here. - Hello.
So for today's episode,
I gathered some guys who genuinely love running.
Okay.
I wanted to show you what proper running looked like.
- The proper running? - Yes.
You're such a turncoat.
- You... - Hey.
Hyun Moo is mad for real.
Hyun Moo.
I've never seen him this charismatic before.
Na Ra is suddenly getting thirsty.
(Na Ra was a member of the Fun Run Crew.)
Gosh. That's true!
(Transferring to the Proper Run Crew)
Well, that's how life works.
I was just camping there. And they showed up there.
(That's the excuse he comes up with.)
- Hyun Moo. - Ji Hyeon won't walk out...
from the adjacent tent, right?
- "Hey!" - Gosh, no.
- Ji Hyeon, you can't switch. - I don't do that.
- What do you mean? - He's disappointed.
- You're making Na Ra look bad. - You won't do that?
Wait. You want to run fast now?
(He has no excuse to offer now.)
You're here.
- Hello. - Gosh.
- Hello. Gosh. - Hello.
- Come on. What is this? - Hey.
- You're already sweating. - Yes.
- Thank you for doing everything. - It rained...
- Okay. - when I was pitching the tent.
- Right. - Yes.
(It poured down when he was pitching the tent.)
It poured down...
- when I was pitching the tent. - That serves you right.
(That serves you right.)
It's like a scene in a drama.
(He finishes setting it up while getting drenched in rain.)
I didn't know he had to do it in the rain.
My gosh. But that must've been a lot of work.
That's not easy.
Gosh, look at your outfit.
What? No, you don't have to do that.
It was a long trip, wasn't it?
No, we got here faster than we thought. Talking about running...
I saw him paint a bit in his atelier.
- Really? - Yes.
We were in my atelier for a bit.
- Really? - Why... You startled me.
- What? You suddenly... - What are you doing?
- Hold on. You're doing that a lot. - Really?
(He's taking off his clothes again?)
- You keep stripping. - Come on, Kian84.
- I'm getting ready to run. - You took off your suit earlier...
and now your pants.
- He did the same thing earlier. - Really?
- You know what? - Yes.
Let's give today a try. If we make a good team,
let's try the 10km marathon together.
- I love it. - Okay.
We could do so many things as runners.
I always ask MINHO.
"How many kilometers do you run?"
"What have you been doing for your exercise lately?"
As we discussed this a lot,
we decided to pick a day and go for a run together.
MINHO and I planned it.
Just like I asked many questions to MINHO,
this guy asked me many questions.
It was Na Ra.
(In the car during the summer retreat)
(I always run alone.)
(Sometimes, it gets boring.)
(Let's run together.)
(He appealed to Kian84 with his passion for running.)
Then I thought the three of us should do it.
So the three of us ended up coming here for a run.
(The eldest and crew chief, Kian84)
(He doesn't stop running even in extreme conditions.)
- Gosh, he's so fast. - That was just crazy.
(He participated in the HYROX Taipei event.)
- Gosh. - He's just on another level.
- He won 1st place. - He won 1st place.
- That was just crazy. - That's...
He won first place in Asia.
(He built his stamina through regular routines.)
He's a comedian.
(Energizer Na Ra with endless energy)
I thought, "It's finally happening."
I tend to put a lot of emphasis on the beginning.
Like your first crush.
- Or... - This is making me want to vomit.
your first experiences.
I value them a lot.
And running with Kian84 for the 1st time...
really excited me.
So I had trouble going to sleep.
- I was that excited. - Gosh, really? It's just a run.
(Shy)
(Eyes closed)
I was touched.
I wanted to run with Kian84.
I like Kian84.
I actually picked up running...
after watching Kian84.
- My gosh. They weren't meant to be. - His TV shows...
- I really liked your TV shows. - Thank you.
I watched all of his shows.
As a runner, he was my role model.
And being asked to run with him...
made me so happy and emotional even.
Gosh. You were that happy?
(Smiling)
- We can go abroad... - Yes.
and run with the crew there.
- We could do a lot with running. - There are so many things to do.
- So I heard about your age. - Yes.
You were born in 1990?
I was born in early 1991.
All of my friends were born in 1990.
Are you more comfortable if I address you as an older brother?
- Whatever you feel comfortable. - It doesn't matter to me at all.
- Really? - Wait.
Then...
- I was born on December 9, 1991. - December 9.
- I was born in January. - Then we're almost 11 months apart.
So we're almost a year apart.
- Treat me as an older brother. - Yes, you are.
My brother, Na Ra.
I should've done that from the get-go.
- That's more comfortable for me. - The social titles got messed up.
(Joking)
Seriously.
Will you... Wait. Will he know after today?
If the Fun Run is better for him?
- Besides, - Once he does a proper run?
the Fun Run Crew is all fake.
- That's true. - It's all fake.
- Well... - You were deceived.
- They used you. - He's gaslighting Na Ra.
How fast did you run? Did it take 20 minutes to run 1km?
It was over 20 minutes.
- Was it 26 minutes? - It was 26 minutes?
What do you think about taking 26 minutes to run 1km?
(Jogging lightly, so their knees don't hurt)
(They freely ate and hung out while running.)
He had so much fun.
(Happiness was more important than records for the Fun Run Crew.)
Bring that T-shirt back next week.
- You must return it. - I thought he could keep it.
- He can't keep it? - No, he can't.
Oh, no. He's sad. His eyes are wet.
- Right. - His eyes are getting wet.
(Teary)
You have the physique of a good runner.
- His body is built to hit a low 40. - Look at his ankles.
- At the competitions, - Okay.
there's a category for skilled amateurs.
And those runners have a specific build.
- And you have the same build. - He's one of them.
Na Ra looks like a magazine model for a running brand.
- He's got that build. - Seriously. His figure...
- Should we start running? - Let's go.
I'll go inside and change.
Okay.
- You can change here. - It doesn't matter.
All right. Let's warm up.
- Just the ankles. - Let's do some taping.
I'll tape only my ankles.
(I'll tape only my ankles.)
- My ankles weakened a bit. - Hey.
This is...
- The ligament? - Yes, my ligament.
- But... - Gosh, this is nice.
I think taping does help.
(The crew chief personally puts on tapes on his ankles.)
Do you have a warm-up routine?
- I'll follow yours. - I have one.
- Here it goes. - Okay.
- Circle your wrists and ankles. - Wrists and ankles.
One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven.
- One, two. - One, two.
- One, two. Two. - Two.
- One, two, three. - Three.
- One, two, three, four. - Gosh.
- One, two, three. - They could keep up very well.
- Five. - One, two, three.
- Six. - Two, three, four,
- five, six. - Five.
My heart rate is up.
I thought that was a bad thing.
- It should be elevated a bit. - No, that's a good thing.
- We need to get the blood flowing. - Yes.
It's exhausting.
Let's get going now.
I don't know where we're going.
- We're going to start here. - Okay.
It was the first time I was running with MINHO...
and Na Ra.
Instead of running in the city, I wanted us to do trail running.
It would be different.
- Trailing running is a mix... - My gosh.
of hiking and marathons.
They're running on mountains.
I did that when I trained as a judo player.
I woke up at 4am every day.
I stretched and then went up to the mountain.
Track and field athletes do that. Right?
You go up to the top and then come back down.
You're one of us then.
My gosh.
- She was young back then. - Thinking about that...
still makes me feel dizzy. Seriously.
Right.
Running on mountains will be really tough.
So afterward, it improves your record on flatland.
Avid runners do a lot of trail running.
- It's like a new genre. - It's a training exercise.
We're at Mount Ilja.
Mount Ilja. I guess it's straight.
This is a very popular mountain...
for trail runners.
Lee Bong Ju also used to run here a lot.
A lot of enthusiastic runners go to that mountain.
We're going to set out from the campsite and go up.
Then we'll come to our first turning point.
We'll keep running.
Past the summit, we'll reach the second turning point.
From there, we'll return to the campsite.
Then the total distance of the trail run will be 7.8km.
What kind of shape is that?
Because people name the run after the shape?
- It looks like a dustpan. - What?
- Don't say that. - A dustpan?
- The Dustpan Run. - I haven't heard that in a while.
- The Dustpan Run. - That's the most infuriating.
(Talking about the shape is the most infuriating.)
I hate that.
I only had the shape of the whale in my head.
- The whale? - I'm determined to crush the whale.
(Sad)
Catch the whale.
I really liked it.
Once you're good at trail running, you'll be good at road running.
I wanted us to have fun with the run today.
That's what I thought when we began.
I don't see any excitement in your eyes.
- I was determined that day. - Seriously. You look so determined.
I was quite serious about it too.
I was quite serious.
It felt like the battlefield of men...
who gathered to do some real running.
(Disappointed)
- Let's go. We got this. - Okay. Let's go. We got this.
We started running in the most serious manner.
The three of us didn't talk. We were quiet.
- Yes. We were quiet. - That's how we started our run.
- Right. We focused on its essence. - We focused on its essence.
- We didn't have to be chatty. - Right.
- We didn't do that. - We just...
You guys are the chattiest right now.
- We didn't talk then. - We focused on its essence.
- So we're talking now. - Right.
(The Proper Run Crew enters the trail course.)
- Gosh. - By the way,
it's nice that there are trees.
- Yes. It's nice and cool. - Yes.
This is the upside of trail running. Looking at the scenery...
doesn't get boring.
(Looking at the scenery is one of the perks.)
(MINHO is running slightly ahead of them.)
MINHO wants to run a bit faster.
- Right. - I bet.
I bet there's a bit of rivalry between MINHO and Kian84.
What rivalry? He's my crew chief.
(Retching)
(Glancing)
- Gosh, I love this trail. - It's cool.
With trail running,
- we can admire the view. - Right.
It's a different vibe from the road.
The scent of grass definitely improves your mood.
- I love this trail. - Yes.
Especially during summer when the sun is too strong,
- it's cooler in the mountains. - There are shaded areas too.
- Mountains are better. - They are.
Staying home is better.
- Right. You do have a point. - It's cool in the house.
True.
I hope the course stays flat.
If it's flat like this...
- It'd be perfect. - Yes.
- Gosh. We should be careful here. - Be careful.
(They enter the mountainous path.)
Man, there's an uphill already.
Gosh, there's an uphill right away.
With this kind of uphill...
I usually run slower. Actually, this pace...
- Okay. - is quite fast.
We can take it slow.
(They run, following MINHO's lead.)
We got this.
(We got this.)
You should go in front.
(A narrow path)
- Gosh, be careful. - Oh, stairs.
- Oh, it's mud. - Mud.
(A muddy trail)
- Be careful. - It rained that morning.
- So the path was slippery. - Oh, no.
Gosh, the excruciating stairs.
(After the muddy path, they enter the excruciating stairs.)
- Be careful. - We're done for.
- Oh, my. It's endless. - What is this?
The first stretch of the trail was pretty steep.
Oh, my.
(Silence fills the air with the endless stairs.)
(Campsite, Turning Point 1, Turning Point 2)
(Campsite, Turning Point 1)
(The members of the Proper Run Crew run up the endless stairs.)
(Taking off his cap)
(Panting)
- Gosh, I love these stairs. - Oh, my.
MINHO kept on running up without getting tired.
Gosh, MINHO is just getting started.
(The crew chief is leading his crew in the front.)
- MINHO, you go first. - Okay.
(The stairs are slowing the older members down.)
Should we go slower?
- Hey. No. Keep going. - Okay.
The stairs are endless.
This is crazy.
Is this for real?
This is how trail running goes.
- This is the hard part. - This is trail running?
This is trail running.
(As he runs up the endless stairs,)
(Na Ra is starting to get tired.)
(Glancing back)
- MINHO, you're not even panting. - Yes? What?
- You're breathing, right? - My breathing is pretty good.
(Stopping)
- I knew it. - Let's walk here for a bit.
Let's walk. Okay.
That's different from running.
- Right. - It's so different.
Exactly.
(Only the sounds of heavy breathing fill the air.)
Hey.
(Look at that.)
What is it? One hundred eight? One hundred eighty?
(His heart rate is at 180.)
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
Call an ambulance.
(Joking)
It's dangerous if your heart rate goes over 180.
You should slow down.
- Actually, - He has to stop.
when you want to hit a personal best,
it has to hover around 190.
- Hover around there? - Was that the dead point?
- It was the dead point. - It is.
I didn't know.
(They finally finish climbing up the stairs.)
Gosh. I...
I'm not in shape.
- Mine went up to 160. - How's your breathing?
Eight minutes and fifty-six seconds.
(Campsite, Turning Point 1, Turning Point 2)
It was quite hilly. So our pace is pretty good.
- It's a downhill. - Yes.
Recovery.
- Now, when you run, - Recovery.
don't tense up your legs.
Focus on your toes.
- Put weight on our toes. Great. - Recovery.
An uphill is always followed by a downhill.
(Glancing back)
You're okay, right?
- No? - What? I'm okay.
- Watch your feet. - Are you okay?
Na Ra, are you okay?
(Instead of answering him, Na Ra only breathes heavily.)
(Even though he's struggling, Na Ra keeps up with them.)
(The momentum builds up from the downhill.)
This is so fun.
- I love it. - He was smiling while running.
- You were also smiling. - I started to have fun.
Only Na Ra isn't smiling.
He's not talking at all.
- At that moment, - Yes.
did you think about the Fun Run?
- Oh, I... - You did, didn't you? Be honest.
- Can I be honest? - You're walking a lot now.
I didn't think about the Fun Run.
- What? - I see.
I just wanted to lock in and focus on the present while running.
- That was my determination. - Right.
Hyun Moo, I get that you're sad.
But don't scowl at him. That's not cool.
- Seriously. - I'm holding myself back.
(Whining)
He's got a soft punch.
(Calm down, Hyun Moo.)
(Na Ra is focused on trail running instead of the Fun Run.)
My gosh. This is only fun...
- because we're running together. - Yes.
Will I be able to do this alone?
- Let's run together. - We can do this together then.
- Great. Thank you. - We can do it together.
- Yes. - Thank you.
Running with other people is much more fun.
Me too. I wanted to run with MINHO. So it's nice to run together today.
You would've given up if you were alone.
- I would've given up. - Right.
No one could do that alone.
(As they run with their members of the crew...)
We're out of the mountain.
(they finally reach their first turning point.)
- This was our first turning point. - My gosh.
No more mountains. Here's an asphalt road.
(Campsite, Turning Point 1, Turning Point 2)
We reached our first turning point.
- And we ran 2.3km. - Hey. I'm wet.
- I'm wet. - We ran for 18 minutes.
- Eighteen minutes? - Yes.
- You ran for 18 minutes? - Yes.
You guys are sweating profusely.
How do you feel now?
When I run 5km, my shirt gets soaked...
- It gets wet like this after 7km. - Don't people do that...
during marathons?
- There are usually water stations. - Right.
There are no water stations...
- during trail running. - You can't get water.
So I brought water.
- It's refreshing. - I have my own routine.
(Out of breath)
We're at our first turning point. I've got something for us.
- Let's fuel up on our energy. - Right.
(He takes something out from his pocket.)
- This is it. I swear. - Okay.
- I take it during HIIT. - What's that?
- It boosts my energy magically. - Really?
I swear. I experienced it myself.
It's mostly carbs.
So you get an energy boost.
This will be super helpful.
Pineapples.
I like pineapple flavors.
- Isn't it good? - Yes.
When I do high-intensity interval training these days,
- I have to take this. - Right.
It boosts my performance too.
We're at our first turning point.
Should we maintain the same pace?
- I'm good. - Sounds good.
Let's boost our energy and keep running.
- We got this. - I can put them back in here.
(He puts away the wrappers in his pocket.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(Running wearily)
Wait, there it is. It's his signature form.
(He takes this running form whenever he's exhausted.)
Let's go!
- Gosh. - We got this.
We got this.
(The Proper Run Crew goes back into the mountain.)
My thighs are killing me after the break.
My gosh, they're killing me.
(Campsite, Turning Point 1, Turning Point 2)
(Their energy is fully charged.)
- Let's do 3km. - Let's do 3km.
- Let's do 7 minutes and 30 seconds. - Okay.
(They pick up the pace after the break.)
- He was no joke. He was barefoot. - Barefoot?
- What? - Gosh.
- He's running barefoot? - My gosh.
That's Kian84 when he gets older.
- He might be doing just that. - He's Kian84's future.
(As they run past the barefooted pro,)
(they focus on trail running again.)
(Repeatedly going uphill and downhill)
Gosh, the stairs.
- Darn it. - Let's do this.
(Na Ra is tired and ends up walking.)
- Let's slow down on the stairs. - Yes.
(But MINHO is doing fine.)
(Panting)
Gosh, MINHO's breathing was so stable.
(On the other hand, the older members are drained.)
- Kian84. Why do trail running? - Yes?
Trail running?
Trail running makes road running...
- much easier. - Really?
Yes.
(The crew chief resumes running after encouraging him.)
(Na Ra follow the crew chief and runs again.)
If we keep walking, we'll lose our rhythm.
- Na Ra, you're okay. Right? - I'm okay.
- Okay. - I'm not okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
Wait. Na Ra is exhausted.
(Na Ra keeps on trying and catches up with them.)
Don't tense up your thighs. Focus on your toes.
- Toes. - Engage your toes.
- Toes. - Yes.
(He starts running and stops soon afterward.)
Na Ra was the ace member...
- during the Fun Run. - I know.
He ran while smiling like a carp.
- He was the winner among us. - That's right.
Things are different now.
What's the point of doing something that doesn't make us smile?
I think it was when we were past 2km.
My vision turned blurry,
and my body became slow.
The weather was hot, my body was sweaty,
- my legs hurt, - That's right.
and I was out of breath.
You weren't used to running in the mountains.
My body and mind weren't in sync.
It was so exhausting, and my vision was blurry.
You should've had bread during the run.
- You should've had bread. - You didn't go to a supermarket.
- That's right. - Was that the reason?
(You should have carbs during a run.)
(It'll clear up your vision.)
You were good during the Fun Run because you ate bread.
(There was a reason why we did that during the Fun Run, okay?)
Na Ra, are you okay?
- What? - Are you okay?
Who are you?
Who... Who are you?
- Na Ra. - Yes?
- Relax your shoulders. - Relax my shoulders?
- Relax your shoulders. - Okay.
- My shoulders feel tight. - Relax your shoulders...
- and tighten up your nose. - Good.
He led me with a sense of responsibility.
- I was so thankful. - You'll breathe more easily.
It's important to have someone who cheers you on by your side.
All of us run well. This is incredible.
(Kian84 and MINHO look trustworthy in front of Na Ra.)
Okay. Our pace is 7 minutes and 40 seconds per km.
- Okay. - We kept up with the pace.
Nice.
- They've run at that pace for 4km. - They're fast.
Our pace is really good right now.
We might enter the six-minute range at this rate.
- Really? - Yes.
In the mountains...
We did it! We're at 5km, and the pace is 6 minutes and 46 seconds.
- Six minutes and forty-six seconds. - This is insane.
We're good at setting the pace.
Nice.
I think both of you run very well.
I think we can go more slowly.
Hey.
- We should keep up with the pace. - "I think we can go more slowly."
(That didn't work.)
Your body becomes more tired when you walk.
(They gather up their strength and keep up with the pace.)
This is Turning Point Two.
(They arrive at Turing Point 2.)
(Exhausted)
How many kilometers have you run?
Over 5km.
Turning Point Two.
Shall we have a short break?
We have a bit of water left.
- It felt like a dream. - Drink first.
- No, drink first. - Thank you.
(He gives water to Na Ra since he is struggling the most.)
- MINHO, did you drink water? - I'm okay, Kian84.
(He drinks water after looking after the crew members.)
My facial expression is bad.
It's bad.
You should've just eaten rice or glass noodles...
at my place.
(Taking out)
- It's wet, but... - It's okay.
What is it?
- Really? - Right. He needs red bean jelly.
Thanks.
I was moved at that moment.
You need to eat to keep going.
(The crew chief has a sweet treat thanks to MINHO.)
(Chewing)
(He takes a bite after taking care of the older members.)
- Let's go. Let's set off. - Okay.
- Let's go! - Okay, let's do this!
- Let's go. Let's do this. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They set off for the campsite.)
- The next section is 1.5km long. - Will they start running again?
I bet I had lost about 1.5kg.
- I know. - I bet I had lost all the water.
(That's incredible.)
- MINHO, be the pacemaker. - Okay.
- Shall I lead? - Yes.
He is cool.
(Speeding up)
MINHO moved to the front and back...
- to push us. - He pushed us from the back...
- Yes. - and pulled us from the front.
It's hard to run after a break.
Right? It's like that.
- Is it the same for you? - It's hard at first...
if you resume running after a break.
It takes a while to get used to the pace again.
Since it's steep, we'll run slowly.
Slowly.
Let's take small steps to go up.
Our pacemaker is very good.
- Seriously. - He is amazing.
Let's take small steps instead of stopping.
- You have to use your glutes here. - Glutes.
Use your glutes.
(MINHO leads the older members while coaching them constantly.)
- Small steps. - Small steps.
- Small steps. Glutes. - Use your glutes.
This way.
If you keep walking, your legs will give out.
- Don't do that. - Okay.
All right.
(With MINHO's encouragement)
- Okay. We're at 6km. - Okay.
The pace is 8 minutes and 44 seconds.
(Na Ra follows them well with small steps.)
Your legs aren't too tired, right? It was okay, right?
- It was okay. - Yes.
- It was much better than before. - Yes.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- The best runner... - Let's go.
- needs to be at the front. - That's right.
- Then it's easy to follow him. - I agree.
Watch the stairs. Let's take small steps.
- Small steps. - No big steps.
(They take small steps for the stairs as well.)
(Why is Na Ra taking big steps?)
- I had no strength in my legs. - I see.
His strength is gone.
This way, your feet won't get tired.
I think Na Ra's skin tone looks weird.
- I know. - It's ashen.
He looks like a ghost on MINHO's shoulder.
That's scary. Stop it.
(Glancing over)
Na Ra, your steps are too big.
- I... - You're taking strides.
- If I take small steps, - Small steps.
my hip joints hurt.
My hip joints hurt.
- How do they hurt? - They get pinched.
- They get pinched. - Yes.
- Do they get pinched? - They get pinched.
So I keep taking big steps.
It'll be very exhausting to take big steps.
If I take big steps...
like you and MINHO say, I get tired right away.
Na Ra, let's go at your pace for the last section.
(Na Ra, let's go at your pace for the last section.)
- Na Ra, - Yes?
go at the pace that feels comfortable to you.
We'll follow you.
(But his stamina reaches its limits.)
He is walking.
- Take the lead. - Hurry up and run.
My heart rate is 188bpm.
- MINHO, set the pace. - Is his heart rate 188bpm?
- MINHO, go ahead. - MINHO, be the pacemaker.
Okay.
(In the end, MINHO becomes the pacemaker again.)
- MINHO and Kian84 are incredible. - Let's go.
How are they so athletic?
It was a crisis.
I had one crisis after another.
"I want to run well. But I won't be able to run well."
"No, I'll run well."
"But I won't be able to run well." I had those thoughts...
over and over again.
(He follows them as if his life depends on it.)
(Grabbing)
(Will Na Ra get a helping hand?)
Hold on a second.
(He follows them as if his life depends on it.)
(Grabbing)
(The crew chief holds his wrist.)
Hold on a second.
(Na Ra, you can do it.)
I didn't know there was such a heartfelt moment.
(Praising himself)
Seriously.
It was one spoonful and gratitude...
and the thought, "Please let go of me."
(Please let go of me.)
(Chuckling)
- "Stop!" - Ten spoonfuls of that.
"Stop!"
- "Please let go of me." - I was too exhausted.
We're nearly there.
We were nearly at the end.
- I know. - Walking at the end...
would've made him regretful.
- That's right. - So I encouraged him...
- to run until the end. - My goodness.
(He pushes Na Ra from the back until the very end.)
- We're nearly there. - Let's cheer up.
(They're close to the campsite now.)
Keep following me.
(Exhausted)
Kian84, be the pacemaker.
- All right. - Okay.
- Let's stay close together. - We keep going faster.
No, we aren't going fast.
(All right. Let's do this.)
(I did 2 people's worth in the Fun Run Crew.)
He was a completely different person.
You belong in the Fun Run Crew.
You're the ace member in the Fun Run Crew.
You're the ace member.
- Be the head of a snake. - Be the head of a snake,
not the tail of a dragon.
The head of a snake is better than the tail of a dragon.
- The head of a snake is better. - That's right.
- You can do it. - All right.
(Someone save the tail.)
I always have this thought when things get hard at the end.
"To do this,"
"I endured all those hardships."
I still keep those words close to my heart.
How cool. They're like special forces.
This is the moment you get a workout.
This way.
(They've braved strong winds...)
(and rough waves.)
We're nearly there. I see the starting point.
- Let's run at full speed. - Okay.
- Let's run. - Let's go.
- Run at full speed? - Let's go.
(Every member...)
(of the crew...)
(runs at full speed toward the finish line.)
(They pass the finish line as one.)
Na Ra.
(We did it.)
(They succeed in completing about 8km of trail running.)
We did it. Let's walk.
Watching this after the Fun Run...
really makes me see the difference.
Right? There is a big difference.
- We thought we were cool. - "This isn't it."
You were cool, Ji Hyeon.
We were cool.
- You won't get that taste. - You really won't.
(Triumphant)
- You ran really well. - We did 8km of trail running.
It's my first time doing such a thing without a break.
Usually, my legs give out when I reach the finish line.
But this is...
- Both are hard, but it's better. - You have strength in your legs.
- It's a bit better. - Yes. Both are hard. Exactly.
- But your legs get less tired. - It's a bit better.
I see.
- My goodness. Hold on. - Still...
That's Na Ra's grandpa.
Isn't that Na Ra's grandpa?
- I feel so bad. - Don't be.
He has three bags under his eyes.
It's like...
He has three bags under his eyes. I should draw him again.
(Exhaustion multiplied the bags under his eyes.)
I should draw three bags under his eyes.
(He plans to retouch his masterpiece.)
He was in Zone Five...
- throughout 8km. - That's right. He held out.
By your heart rate, the intensity of the workout...
gets divided into six zones.
Zone Five is right below the maximum heart rate.
Keeping that up while running is the hardest.
Most people can't even hold out for two minutes.
- I would've turned back. - Na Ra held out.
- Fun Run Crew is in Zone Two. - That's right.
- When you're in Zone 5, - Zone 5.
you continue to hit your limits.
- It's a high-intensity workout. - Totally.
- If you look at the records... - He held out.
- He held out. - He held out.
(Embarrassed)
- Do you want some cold water? - Yes. Cold water.
- Let's drink ice water. - Ice water.
Let's drink ice water.
I feel faint.
(Drained)
Kian84, cheers.
- Kian84. - Yes.
(Well done, everyone.)
It really recharges you.
I bet it tastes amazing.
- Seriously. - It's insane.
- I bet it tastes amazing. - I bet it's ice cold.
I felt a sense of accomplishment.
As MINHO said, running until the end...
made me feel good.
Gosh, I'm so happy.
I regained this much consciousness.
- Did you get it back? - By this much.
Well done.
- You're the best at holding out. - I know. You held out very well.
- I... - Thank you.
Not even MINHO can hold out for long...
- in Zone Five. - It'll be hard for me.
Kian84 grabbed my arm and ran.
You know,
you kept talking to us when you were the pacemaker.
It kept us going.
Since it's steep, we'll run slowly.
(He motivated them to move forward...)
(with his heartfelt words.)
- You need such friends to run... - That's right.
in a high-intensity training zone.
(Such a friend is a must!)
When you run without a word,
- it gets very lonely. - I know. It gets lonely.
It isn't fun. It feels like you're training.
MINHO, let's see how many calories we've burned.
- We've burned 732kcal. - Did you say 732kcal?
- Did you burn 732kcal? - By running 8km.
In an hour?
In an hour.
The elevation was 338m.
Did you say 338m?
That's like going up the 63 Building.
Seriously.
We went up a lot.
We ran more than going up the 63 Building.
Exactly.
Our average pace is 7 minutes and 43 seconds per km.
We ran so fast.
Seven minutes and forty-three seconds?
We ran uphill most of the time.
- For trail running? - We ran really well.
You improve by running with a better runner.
- I think you're right. - You improve a lot.
Who is this?
- I don't think that's Na Ra. - I know.
- He looks familiar. - We're about the same.
You know, I had this thought.
If we stop...
right here,
I'm 100 percent sure that Hyun Moo will go,
"They didn't run as many kilometers as we did."
We win when it comes to kilometers.
(We ran 12.6km.)
To be honest, nothing he says bothers me.
To be honest, it's meaningless.
It doesn't bother me either,
- but it's like this. - What?
I know that he'll make fun of us, so...
- So... - Does it mean it bothers me?
- You want to be free of faults. - Do you call that a run?
- I want to crush him. - You want to crush him.
How many kilometers did the Fun Run Crew run?
- They ran 12km. - For goodness' sake.
See? It bothers you.
It annoys me that it bothers me.
- It annoys me too. - Why did he make...
that lousy crew? It annoys me so much.
"That lousy team?"
- Hey! Ji Hyeon is in the crew! - Why does the crew bother me?
- Ji Hyeon is in the crew! - We're...
- a good crew. - "That lousy crew?"
- It's nice to run slowly. - That's right.
Running needs a new trend.
That's right. Ji Hyeon is good.
For goodness' sake.
I think it's really nice.
Whether it's a Fun Run or an actual run,
people who get along...
- meet up and do something. - It's really nice.
- It's not easy to do that. - That's right.
It's really hard to do that.
- It annoys me too. - Why did he make that lousy crew?
It annoys me so much.
(The man who is in both crews becomes uncomfortable.)
- He is in the middle. - You aren't in that crew anymore.
- You never know. - What?
- We need to treat him well. - Why?
What if he goes back to that crew?
Na Ra might do that.
(Feeling uncomfortable)
He won't do that. No way.
"He won't do that. No way."
I was worried that he'd go back since our run was exhausting.
You guys didn't even feed him.
- "He won't do that. No way." - He won't do that. Come on.
Since Na Ra held out really well,
he wouldn't need to go back to the Fun Run Crew.
Let's have the second round.
There is a trail people use...
- for a run. - Okay.
- One set is 4km. - Okay.
- Let's have one set. - One set?
- Will they run again? - One more set.
- Will they run again? - Let's run.
- That's insane. - Will they run again?
That's a good idea.
Will it be okay?
Just once.
(Excited)
- Sounds good. - Let's have one more set.
- Sounds good. - He is a fighter.
Na Ra doesn't give up.
I didn't want to appear weak.
Na Ra really is a fighter.
Are they preparing for an international sports event?
- Are they at the training center? - Exactly.
But the second trail had...
- fewer uphills. - It was flatter.
- A plain? - Yes.
The second run. Let's go.
Will they run again? I can't believe them.
Here we go again.
Okay.
The second round in the mountains.
Running twice in the mountains can't be easy.
(They pick up the speed from the beginning.)
Shall we turn it into a proper workout?
Shall we each go at our own pace?
Okay. Shall we go?
It's a good idea to go at one's own pace.
They still have energy.
MINHO is fast.
(As soon as they decide to go at their own pace)
- He's running at full speed. - Gosh, he is like a water deer.
I wanted to run at full speed.
Retrievers need to be unleashed so that they can run freely.
(No brakes)
Okay. The pace is 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
He ran so fast.
I succeeded in it!
The pace of 4 minutes and 30 seconds in the mountains?
- He is insane. - MINHO didn't run properly before.
(Kian84 is right behind him.)
(He has experience in running.)
(He runs at a relaxed pace.)
He is an experienced runner.
(Retching)
That's a sign for you to go home.
I want to walk.
Walking makes it harder.
No, I want to walk.
- It was a solo fight. - Walking makes it harder.
- It was a solo fight. - No, I want to walk.
Let's run together for the last bit.
(Hurry over here.)
- Let's go. - You need to run together.
(They run at full speed toward the finish line.)
- We picked up the speed. - They're fast.
It's a matter of pride.
Let's speed up until the end.
- We're nearly there. - Let's go.
- Let's do this. - Let's go.
- We're nearly there. A bit more. - Na Ra.
- Speed up a bit more. - Na Ra.
Na Ra, come on.
- I gritted my teeth and ran. - A bit more.
A bit more. You can do it.
- We're nearly there. - Okay.
- Okay. - A bit more.
- Hey. - Come on.
(Finally, they reach the finish line.)
- They arrived at the end. - I'm exhausted.
They did it.
(That's impressive.)
Well done.
- Let's go. - We ran about 13km to 14km...
- for trail running. - We ran 13km.
(Total distance: About 13km)
Total elevation was 468m.
That's the same as going up the 63 Building 2 times.
(It's like running the 63 Building 1.9 times.)
(The three of them completed the real run.)
I wasn't going to point it out,
but we ran 1km more than the Fun Run Crew.
(We ran 1km more than the Fun Run Crew.)
We're on their minds.
If we count in the elevation,
- we ran about 20km. - That's right.
But the Fun Run Crew had an elevation too.
- That's right. - We had it worse.
(Uphill!)
- It was very dangerous. - I know.
(The uphill was so dangerous.)
My heart rate was 190bpm.
(His heart ran at full speed as well.)
I'm dying.
- You have remaining stamina, right? - A little bit.
He is a monster.
- You have remaining stamina, right? - Go and have another round.
- We need to do it together. - Right.
We had good teamwork...
considering that it was our first time.
To MINHO, the pace must've been slower...
- I know. - than his usual one.
But he slowed down for us. I'm grateful for that.
(He is thankful that MINHO ran with them.)
As for Na Ra, the pace was much faster...
than his usual one.
But he kept up until the end. I'm grateful for that.
I'm grateful for both of them.
Yes.
Would it have been possible for Moo Do Ra Ji?
- Come on! - Let me explain.
- Gosh! - Na Ra!
- Na Ra... - Gosh!
says unnecessary things.
- Right. - Na Ra!
- He opened a can of worms. - He asks for trouble.
I should find two more people when he leaves.
- Sunmoo! - Sunmoo?
- Uphill! - Uphill!
(The Fun Run is open to any kind.)
He's the fastest one around me.
(Future Fun Run ace, Sunmoo?)
Sit here. Your legs shouldn't stiffen up.
(Faltering)
Sit on a higher place.
(They arrive at the campsite while sweating buckets.)
- Run in the mountains? - Look at my sweat.
He's sweating a lot.
Even your sweat looks nice.
Right. Even your sweat looks nice.
The shape of the sweat looks rounder than others.
Did you use a spray?
The shape is...
The shape looks nice and round.
(Even the sweat of the ace shines.)
But keep this in mind. I'm the leader.
Of course.
- Kian84! - Well...
Why think that? I came here because of you.
Actually, MINHO led all of us.
- We did follow your pace. - Right.
Even though I may be a figurehead, I'm the leader.
- Of course, I know that. - You're the leader.
- I'm... - The enforcer?
- No. I'm the training director. - Training director.
- In crews, - The training director?
there are training directors.
I'll be the one to come up with the courses...
- Right. - and be the pacemaker.
Those people are the big shots.
- The training director. - Right.
I'll be the cooking director.
The cooking director? All right.
- I'll always bring ice and drinks. - Right.
- You're the crew leader. - Right.
I'm the training director.
- You're the cooking director. - Cooking director.
- That's great. - We must all have a title.
(They have even distributed their roles.)
Should we wash up first?
- Right. Let's wash up. - We've sweated a lot.
- Let's wash up. - Is there a place we can wash up?
- Over there. - They have showers.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(They move to wash away their sweat.)
(They even take showers together...)
(in the Proper Run Crew.)
I saw everything.
Na Ra...
and MINHO's...
everything.
(Wriggling)
(What did Kian84 see?)
I saw everything.
Na Ra...
and MINHO's...
everything.
(I saw everything.)
- Kian84! - What was that?
(Shocked)
What was that?
- Gosh. - What's wrong with your eyes?
That day, I was a bit...
- Why did you bring your eyebrow up? - I was a bit drunk.
This can become a reason for leaving the crew.
- Don't get the wrong idea. - "Don't get the wrong idea."
That's so disgusting.
The showers had no screens.
- Right. - That's how men wash up together.
- Right. - It felt like being in the army.
Well, that's fine.
It's just his eyes.
He brought his eyebrow up.
They all looked great.
They were healthy young men.
As an athlete,
it was inevitable for me...
to check out their body lines.
I checked how fit their bodies were.
We got a lot closer after running and taking a shower together.
(The crew members got a lot closer.)
That was great. That was a refreshing shower.
Are we going to eat?
- We should eat. - I'm so hungry.
(I Live Alone)
(Filial Piety Scenario)
- "Scenario." - "Filial Piety?"
- What? - Is that his mother's house?
- It's Ju Seung. - It's his mother's house.
(Ju Seung is doing something at his mother's house.)
(Busy)
What are you doing?
So...
- Gosh! - What is that?
I don't think the aged kimchi is ready.
It tastes amazing when you stir-fry aged kimchi.
- His mother is a great cook. - Right.
Right.
I'll add this as well.
(I should get back to work.)
(He hurriedly...)
(starts preparing the tomatoes.)
Get some cold water first.
I'll be visiting an important person with my mom today.
I came to my mother's house to get things prepared.
Ju Seung must be cooking.
Which country eats a lot of tomatoes?
Italy.
Spaghetti.
- It prevents cancer. - He's into something again.
He's been saying that to me for months.
- Tomatoes? - As for tomatoes,
they help with your immune system and build anticancer activities.
They are great in many different aspects.
I felt a lot of change.
- I started drinking tomato juice. - Why am I in outer space?
Why is the background always like that for you?
I was being serious!
That seems like...
(Feeling wronged)
I'm planning to give this important person...
some tomato juice.
- Tomato juice? - Right.
- Tomato juice? - I drink it every day.
I drink around 700ml every day.
Hasn't it been a year since you started?
It hasn't been that long. It has been around half a year.
I'm serious about this. Even with a little bit of sleep,
it feels like I slept for a long time.
- Really? - You look really tired today.
I wasn't able to get any sleep today.
- You look so tired. - I need a little bit of sleep.
Shouldn't you take a nap?
I wasn't able to have any tomato juice for a few days.
(Dumbfounded)
(The magical tomatoes...)
(are thrown into boiling water.)
Done.
Right. When they are thrown into cold water after that,
the peels will come off.
They can't be boiled for too long.
That will get rid of all of the vitamin C.
How long must they be blanched for?
- Around 2 to 3 minutes. - They are blanched.
Right. That's how the peels are removed.
(He carefully removes the peels for the important person.)
Should I slice them up a bit?
(Pressing)
(He struggles to cut it.)
The knife must be really blunt.
Is that so? Take this one.
It's fascinating.
That used to be the best knife.
But the knife that felt blunt worked well,
and the best knife felt blunt.
There's a bit of quantum dynamics.
- "Quantum dynamics?" - What are you saying?
(Dumbfounded)
- What's wrong? Did they fight? - Gosh.
I can't understand it as well. Did they get cursed?
(Putting in)
(He fills up the mixer with the tomatoes.)
(Pouring in yogurt)
- What is that? - So yogurt is added.
(A generous amount of olive oil)
- Olive oil? - It's really good.
(Shall I mix them up now?)
- That looks good. - Right.
It must be really good for the body.
That sweetens it up.
Is it ready?
- Gosh, it looks good. - Gosh.
(I hope that person likes it.)
Abalone.
- It's good. - Is it?
This one seemed to be a favorite.
- Along with the perilla leaves. - Her kimchi...
and side dishes are really good.
- The anchovy jangajji looks good. - The anchovies.
- Gosh. I know how they taste. - How important is this person?
- They're packing so many things. - Who are they going to meet?
Mom, since the house looked empty,
- Yes? - I got this.
What is it?
A summer rug.
A summer rug?
Since you like plants,
I got the deep green color.
The house looked empty after Coco's things were removed.
I wanted to help her make the house look less empty.
It feels quite empty without Coco.
After Coco crossed the Rainbow Bridge,
she struggled to get rid of Coco's things.
Gosh, why are so many dogs passing away?
In my mother's room,
there's Coco's urn,
snacks, and toys.
She left soon after Kkotbun left.
- Really? - Around two weeks later?
It was just around two weeks later.
I wanted to visit her often after that,
but she said she didn't want me to come.
She wanted to spend a few weeks with Coco.
- It must've been tough for her. - Right.
(Ju Seung and Coco had an intense relationship.)
(She looked comfortable with Ju Seung's mother.)
(Coco always followed her around.)
(Ju Seung's mother returned Coco with a greater love.)
This was what broke me heart even more.
His mom cooked for me to comfort my loss.
After the meal, I went, "Stay healthy, Coco."
- But she left after two weeks. - Gosh.
- Gosh. - I know how lonely...
- she would feel alone. - Right.
She must feel so lonely.
- Gosh. Poor thing. - Gosh.
(Coco left 12 years of joyful memories.)
Seeing Coco's photos after a while makes me feel...
I heard...
- my mother carried Coco's urn... - Gosh.
and went to the same places they went to for a walk.
This feeling will last for a while.
It won't disappear easily.
It isn't a slippery type of material.
It will flatten out over time.
Gosh, my legs!
(Let's try sitting on it.)
Can dogs step on this?
- Dogs can step on it. - She must...
- want to raise another dog. - Right.
She's thinking about it.
She's been talking about it quite a lot these days.
I saw Kian84's adoption as well.
(Dalkong, Alkong)
- Right. - My parents also went through...
- a pet loss. - Right.
Sunmoo is being a great son now.
Right.
I think it would be great for her to visit the adoption center.
- Right. - Let's go together.
- That sounds good. My mother... - You should go together.
kept saying we should visit at around Chuseok.
There won't be any dust.
Right.
Green!
Green is a nice match with the plants.
That was why I picked green.
(Feeling proud)
Gosh, what a busy day.
(She gets ready to head out after getting the perfect gift.)
Let's see.
(Coming out)
Here...
and here. You see them, don't you?
Like this.
The melasma. Not the age spots.
Can't you see them?
Can't you see the dark spots?
I can't really see them.
- Listen up, Ju Seung. - Yes?
She wants you to send her to a dermatologist.
"I can't see them." Don't say things like this.
There's a certain language that mothers use.
- They use a certain language. - You can't take a hint.
I made a reservation for her to see a dermatologist.
- Good job. - I made a reservation.
"Gosh, my head hurts so much and it feels dry."
"I can't feel any joy in life." When these things are said,
you should send her on a trip.
There's this one as well.
"Gosh, life is so boring."
This is when you should send her a voucher.
- Or cash. - Right. There's this one.
"You're on a lot of shows these days."
"Everyone is talking about you."
This is when you should give her some money to treat others.
- They all mean something. - That's the mother's language.
- That's the mother's language. - Well said.
Right. That's their language.
- We learn from you again. - I didn't know that.
Whenever I take pictures,
this part looks like this,
and this part looks like this.
It means she wants a facelift.
(It means she wants a facelift.)
Do handstands.
(Do handstands.)
How could she do handstands?
My uncles still do handstands.
They're your uncles.
- Gosh. - They're your uncles.
Since they share the same blood,
- What are you saying? - she might be able to do them.
- Let's get going now. - There are ten minutes left.
Let's go. I'll wear these shoes.
(After getting ready to leave,)
(the mother and son head out of the house.)
Let's go.
(Pressing)
(Tapping)
Now, this part...
under my eyes starts to pop out.
(What?)
- Right. - Hey.
You should've driven straight to the dermatologist.
- Go straight to Gangnam. - Right.
This is why you have to take care of your scalp.
- What are you saying? - What are you saying?
(Even I know what she's saying.)
She's crying out for a facelift.
She's crying out for a facelift!
She's crying that out. Why couldn't you realize that?
The scalp is just like the skin. The scalp is another face.
(After struggling to understand the mother's language,)
(they arrive at the place of the important person.)
- "Important person?" - Who is the important person?
- The important person. - The important person.
Gosh, my legs hurt.
I'm here, Mother!
- "Mother?" - Gosh!
Grandma!
This was Ju Seung's grandfather's house.
You're dressed nicely today.
The house is really clean.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
She's so adorable.
(Touching her hair)
This is my grandmother's house.
Her name is Park Kye Soon.
She's 94 years old.
Her skin looks great.
She always takes care of her fashion.
She's a Seongsu-dong icon.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- She's so stylish. - She's stylish.
She was born and raised in Seongsu-dong.
The original fashionista.
Whether it be makeup or skincare,
(Makeup and skincare as well as fashion)
she has been obsessed with how she looks for over 70 years.
I believe she's the most well-known in Seongsu-dong for that.
- Check out her earrings. - Right.
- She has more style than I do. - Right.
Her outfit right now looks really nice.
Right.
After Grandpa passed away,
she has been feeling lonely and crying a lot these days.
As she has been feeling...
(His grandmother struggled after she lost her husband.)
a lot more lonely,
we have come to spend time with her.
Your grandfather passed away?
My grandfather passed away in February.
Your grandfather? Gosh.
You visited often...
- when he was alive. - Right.
- Right. Back then, - I'm visiting more often now.
you even got him sheek masks.
My grandmother's house is close by.
I visit her once or twice a week.
Once or twice a week? When elders...
go through a heartbreak,
it greatly affects...
- They age faster. Right. - their health as well.
I must keep her company.
Ju Seung and his mother visit her often.
They're doing an excellent job.
In my opinion, you're the best out of us.
- He's the best. - Right.
- Right. - It's hard to...
- visit our elders often. - He does well...
- to his elders. - He's affectionate.
Grandma!
- Yes? - I blended these tomatoes.
You went through so much work.
- I blended these tomatoes. - Right.
- Drink a cup of this every day. - Okay.
You have to finish this in a week.
(He puts it in the fridge after explaining it to her.)
You have the best character.
Right.
It won't spill, right?
- Grandma, - Yes?
Mom made a few things for lunch.
Why make so many things?
It isn't a lot.
Mom made side dishes and a few other things.
Hold on.
- Did you finish the cockle salad? - Gosh.
- Did you finish the cockle salad? - I did.
Right. It can't be kept for a long time.
Grandma has been low on energy these days.
Mom visits her often after making side dishes.
That isn't easy to do.
That's amazing of her.
Hold on. What's this?
- It's the sanjeok. - Oh, right.
- It's meat, Grandma. - Got it.
(Nonchalant)
I won't take this out. Make sure to eat this later.
Why did you make so many expensive dishes?
(The different side dishes get taken out...)
(along with a bowl of rice.)
Go and place it like this.
- Just like this. - Okay.
Right.
After Grandpa passed away,
Grandma prepared his meal for every meal.
Oh, I see.
Go and place it there.
(The food is moved to Ju Seung's grandfather's room.)
Gosh.
- Gosh, she's crying. - She's crying.
Her heart must ache so much.
Like this?
(Meanwhile, Ju Seung and his mom)
- The chopsticks must be... - She's crying again.
My gosh.
Enjoy the meal, Grandpa. Mom made it.
She always sounded emotional on the phone.
(Feeling upset)
(Lee Jong Gyu)
(Father, rest in peace.)
After Grandpa passed away,
Grandma couldn't believe it for a while.
And...
she feels that he is in his room.
I understand.
She decided to prepare his meals...
until the 100th day after his death.
(Until the 100th day after his death)
But after the 100th day,
(After the 100th day...)
there wasn't a lot left until Grandpa's birthday,
so she decided to prepare his meals until his birthday.
That's why she has been continuing to prepare his meals.
She talks with him every single day as well.
Right.
They have been together for 70 years.
(The relationship of 70 years is hard to let go of.)
Her best friend in life has left her.
We can never know how that feels. We're just assuming how that feels.
You're crying again!
Let's eat.
Right. Let's get the rice.
Hold on.
Why are you crying again, Grandma?
I told you not to cry!
I'm crying out of joy!
She feels bad about eating the good food on her own.
- Right. - She feels bad about it.
Thank you.
- Gosh. - His mother is crying as well.
They're all crying while looking away.
(Patting)
(Ju Seung calmly comforts his grandmother.)
The tears tend to spread.
I try my best to stay calm.
Right.
- That's needed. - Right.
If Ju Seung ends up crying, they will all end up crying...
- as his mother has a lot of tears. - They will all end up crying.
Have some water before you eat, Grandma.
You're going to get sick.
Come on.
- Don't cry. - Here.
She must feel...
- Hurry up and eat. - You should eat, Grandma.
Thank you for the food.
(The three sit together closely.)
That looks good.
She had to restore her energy.
That's why she put more effort into the food.
His mom's good at taking care of others thoughtfully.
Tell me if it's bad. If it's good...
(Laughing)
- An honest evaluation. - That's right.
(He grabs a grilled abalone.)
Grandma, have some abalone.
I'll have it.
(Taking a bite of the grilled abalone first)
- Is it good? - But Grandma is...
Is it okay, Mom?
(Nodding)
Yes.
You should eat too.
(It's delicious. Go ahead and eat.)
(They finally start eating after seeing Grandma eat.)
(Glancing over)
- Grandma, what's that ring? - You cry all day.
- Is it pearl? - It's black pearl. It's a set.
I just put it on.
That's cool.
She's really stylish.
She always dresses up even at home.
(Staring)
Grandma, the laser treatment removed everything.
- It's clean, right? - Really?
- Really? - This side looks clean too.
Yes.
She recently got a laser treatment to remove the age spots.
I heard it hurts a lot.
(She's a true fashionista.)
Her skin was glowing.
- She did well. - Yes.
You didn't get a lot of sunlight, did you?
I didn't go out.
It's healed now, so you can go out and walk now.
- Yes. - It's healed.
You need to get a lot of sunlight.
You need to get a lot of Vitamin D from sunlight.
You need to keep changing topics.
You know what I mean, right? You need to keep changing topics.
I should finish this.
But it's too much.
Now, she can't...
- eat as much as she used to. - She's eating less.
- Because of digestion... - Right, she can't digest.
- Gosh, that hurts! - What's wrong?
- What happened? - What happened?
- Was there a stone? - What?
- Gosh, it hurts. - What happened?
I keep chewing this side.
I guess there's something wrong with my jaws.
I guess there's something wrong with my jaw.
(Bursting into laughter)
- I'm glad she's laughing. - I keep chewing this side.
Maybe it's because it's too delicious.
Because I'm enjoying the food I made myself?
Grandma is smiling so beautifully.
Gosh, eat slowly.
No one's going to steal.
I mean, this side...
It was okay before.
Gosh, that hurts.
- Gosh. - How...
She chewed her cheek to lighten the mood.
Don't feel too depressed.
I think I'll get better after Grandpa's birthday.
Goodness.
(Getting up)
(Striding in)
(Did you enjoy it, Grandpa?)
The water spilled too?
(Cleaning up Grandpa's dishes too)
This spot is perfect. I put it up here, Grandma.
He must've been happy.
(He must've been happy that his grandson got him a meal.)
Ju Seung blended them...
so you can have tomatoes.
He prepared something.
Wait. What is that?
Grandma, let me show you something.
Show me what?
Grandpa always called me Director Lee.
It was a survival show among directors.
It was a competition between directors.
I joined a competition.
- And I won. I won first place. - Oh, my.
(Ju Seung tried his hand at directing.)
(With an unrivaled directing of a thriller...)
(Director Lee Ju Seung)
(He won first place after a fierce competition.)
Director Lee.
He's always been famous for his writing.
That's why he won.
He's joining his crew now.
I know.
Sung Hwan should take auditions that Ju Seung holds.
Let him go for the audition.
Let's see Ju Seung making it to the Cannes Film Festival.
- He definitely should make it. - He'll make it for sure.
(The future Cannes Film Festival awarded director...)
(returned home with glory.)
(Handing her the winning trophy right away)
She must be really happy.
- I won first place. - Goodness. Well done.
- Gosh. - And won that.
Gosh, Ju Seung, you did it. My goodness.
- Don't cry. - Grandpa...
always called me Director Lee.
I'm sad he didn't get to see me make it.
(Grandpa didn't get to see me become a director.)
I won first place.
Let's take a look at the trophy.
Thank you.
Stay healthy. Health comes first.
Just stay healthy.
- Grandpa would've loved it. - I know. He'd have loved it.
(Grandpa would've loved it.)
Thank you.
I also won prize money for winning first place,
but I donated everything.
Grandpa always told me to always give back.
- I know. - So I donated everything.
- That's so cool. - I donated the entire thing.
There are so many things to learn from him.
I'm really...
Well done.
You donated after winning. Well done.
Grandpa always told you to donate a lot.
(You should share, give, and serve others.)
(You need to be humble. You need to be kind.)
(You'll do well.)
Grandpa...
Ever since I first directed a short movie,
he told me I'd make it as a director.
Whenever I called him,
he called me Director Lee.
(Even on his phone, Ju Seung is saved as Director Lee.)
He called me Director Lee.
While writing the final script for the survival show,
he passed away.
After the funeral, I took some time to pull myself together.
Then I continued writing.
To forget the sadness of his passing,
I immersed myself more into writing.
I feel like Grandpa helped me too.
(Perhaps Grandpa helped him from the skies.)
At the Han River...
He answered.
(The newbie director wrote a script in his room.)
(He used to use a phone to film. After that stage,)
(he completed his dream...)
(of becoming a director page by page.)
(Just as his grandpa predicted, he became Director Lee...)
(who's acknowledged by everyone.)
It felt...
a bit...
Thanks to Grandpa,
I won a great award, so I'm grateful.
Grandpa served others so much...
that he earned respect from that.
He was kind to others.
Because of that mindset,
I donated the whole amount.
I think I did it following his values.
I think it's an award that Grandpa won.
(In the end, it's like an award that Grandpa won.)
That's what I said.
I'm here, Grandpa.
(He always welcomed Ju Seung with a bright smile.)
You're only 73.
(They'd chat for a long time like they're friends.)
Then add the juice here.
(Grandpa he shared anything he found delicious)
- Good. - Is that right?
Grandpa.
(He shows the award to his grandpa as well.)
I won an award thanks to you, Grandpa.
- Let's turn the lights on. - I miss him.
He must've been really happy.
(He turned the donation certificate so he could read it better.)
Goodness.
(Sitting alone in an empty room)
(Staring at the photo of his grandpa)
I really thought my grandpa was watching me.
I felt like I'd cry,
so I talked with him in my heart.
I spent time with him like that.
It's a shame, but if I think that he's watching over me,
- it consoles me a bit. - Right.
It'd have been nice if he saw it in person.
This is my one and only regret.
- What is it? - When I first got into music,
both my grandpa and grandma passed away.
I couldn't show them what I achieved...
- in my career. - Right.
- It must be a big regret. - They were really worried...
because I always wore torn pants.
- They'd sew it. - Grandmas always stitch them up.
- She'd tell me to pull my pants up. - She'd stitch them up with effort.
They must've wondered what I'd become when I grew up.
Of course.
(Massaging)
- Is it aching, Grandma? - Gosh, you startled me.
Does your arm hurt?
No, I just keep massaging it out of habit.
Which part hurts the most these days?
- It hurts everywhere. - It hurts everywhere?
Elders ache everywhere.
What is this skirt, Grandma?
This?
Your aunt got it for me.
- It's beautiful. - Right.
- What is this? Feathers? - It looks airy.
You're good at changing topics.
- That's right. - Nice timing.
- You need to keep changing. - That was sensible of you.
You look wonderful, Mother.
(Twitching her mouth)
- There are pockets too. - What?
There are pockets.
You can't live without pockets.
She got up to show.
She's serious about her style.
(Do you want to see the pockets?)
She's happy.
- It's nice. - It looks like wings.
It looks like a cactus too.
- It's quite hip. - It looks like a cactus too.
- The pockets... - It looks like a flower too.
- Yes. - It's fascinating.
- That's why I like it. - It's wonderful.
You look even more amazing standing up.
Your mother is trying hard.
You can't see it when you're seated.
- Because I was seated. - It's all black.
Yes.
- It looks expensive. - My goodness.
It was 500 dollars after the discount.
It's expensive even after the discount.
She always mentions the price.
- They always mention it. - That's what elders do.
- Every time. - It's important.
My nose looks exactly like yours.
People keep saying that I got a nose job.
But I take after your nose.
What did you say?
My nose looks like yours, right?
- You're right. - So is that bad?
No, people ask me if I got a nose job.
A nose job? I see.
- Your nose... - They say my nose...
keeps getting bigger.
My nose has always gotten bigger.
It'd be better if your face got wider.
- If my face got wider? - If your face got bigger...
(My face getting wider?)
- If his face gets wider? - It's okay.
- Is it? - Yes, it's pretty.
He's pretty because he's my grandson.
- Of course. - Ju Seung is handsome.
He has a lucky nose.
It does seem like your nose got bigger.
- Is that why he's called CORTIS? - My nose keeps getting bigger.
Yes, it's CORTIS.
- My nose is the only thing you see. - That's...
You keep mentioning CORTIS.
- Just call yourself BIGNOSETIS. - It's way bigger now.
BIGNOSETIS?
- BIGNOSETIS. - How could you call him BIGNOSETIS?
That's so weird.
BIGNOSETIS.
He's so witty.
- That's right. - Of course.
When I wake up, I do this 50 times.
Then do this 50 times.
I do this 50 times.
And do 50 times here.
Do this 50 times.
- So she massages her face. - I do this.
- Really? - All my face.
Of course. She does it every day.
Why didn't you tell me?
- How do you do it? Tell me again. - She does it for 40 minutes.
- Here? - No.
- Grab your eyebrows... - My eyebrows.
while lying down.
- Swipe them 50 times. - Do this 50 times.
- Then do this 50 times. - Do this 50 times.
Then do this 50 times too.
Is that why my nose got big?
Her nose got big indeed.
- Then press here. - Press it.
Then lift your face like this.
- Then do this. - Okay.
Do this, and you'll get fewer wrinkles on your neck.
With the massages, I have no problem.
Like this?
Like this? Push it up?
You're the original meridian massage therapist.
Like this.
Elders know that stuff the best.
I do arm exercises too. I do everything for an hour.
(He manages to put her in a better mood...)
(and learns massaging tips.)
The weather is amazing today, Grandma.
- It's a relief. - It's perfect to walk...
since there's not much sunlight.
The day's great.
Shall we get some air?
Is it okay?
I need to put this on.
- Since it's cold... - She's stylish.
Gosh, she put on a beautiful scarf.
Grandma, what about a hat? Aren't you going to put on one?
- A hat? - Put this on.
- The hat is there? - This...
- That's... - It's perfect.
(Putting it on)
She's indeed a Seongsu person.
She's so stylish.
- I knew it. - It goes really well.
- It's so nice. - You look way better with this.
That's right.
Going out for a walk could be an exercise,
but I wanted them...
to get rid of old emotions.
I thought it'd be nice to go for a walk together,
so that's why we went.
(They go out for a walk to refresh themselves.)
- You look great now. - Right.
- It's the best. - Your outfit is amazing, Mother.
I'll be right back. Take care of the house.
Goodness.
(She doesn't forget to say goodbye before going out.)
Grandma, what shoes are you wearing?
Are you wearing these? The ones that look like rubber shoes?
- Is that okay? - Yes.
I can't wear platform shoes.
I only wear these, so they look worn out.
All set.
Gosh, thank you.
- My gosh. - Let's get some air...
and refresh ourselves.
(Full of excitement)
(They go out, feeling excited.)
They're so cool.
- Ju Seung, you're amazing. - He's amazing.
- It's amazing. - You could've changed your car.
- Seriously. - I know.
(He's more incredible, the more I think about it.)
Grandma, we're here.
(They've arrived at a place to take a walk.)
(Taking it out)
The sun isn't that strong, but still...
I'll hold it for you.
Take your time.
(As soon as Grandma gets out,)
(he puts up the sun umbrella.)
Grandma, be careful. You can't use the cane here.
- Goodness. - You can't use the cane here.
Grandma, you walk better than usual today.
It must be because I'm happy.
- You did well. - She walks well.
They sprinkled water here because it's too hot.
(A perfect course for his grandma where it's easy to walk)
The flowers are pretty here.
Goodness.
Gosh, how pretty.
Grandma is still like a little girl.
She likes flowers and pretty things.
(Rummaging)
I should take a photo with my camera.
- Mom, hold this for me. - Photos?
How nice.
Gosh, Director Lee.
He looks different now even with just a camera.
You guys changed because he won first place.
- Gosh. - It makes me see him with bias.
He's so biased.
Is this also that flower?
It looks like Monet's painting.
(Grandma being happy)
- There are thorns. - Don't touch them.
(Director Lee doesn't miss a moment.)
She touches all the flowers.
There are fewer thorns. This doesn't have one.
(Ju Seung's camera)
Gosh, the shot looks different because he's a director.
- Seriously. - That's prejudiced.
Hyun Moo, I had the exact same thought.
I was going to say it, but you said it first.
You were too late.
How did he come up with that shot?
Have you gone mad?
- It's so different. - Gosh, Kian84.
He already has a storyboard in his head.
- With a handheld camera... - I'm envious.
- His hands don't even shake. - The flowers are brought to life.
(She sits on the bench with the help of a master director.)
Goodness.
- You're walking a lot today. - How tiring.
You walk so well. You're like you're in your 60s.
It's because I'm so happy.
- How nice. - She's become a little girl.
Look.
Think of it as the sea. Look over there.
"Dear sea."
"Take good care of my husband."
(A little wish she offers from afar)
Do you think it'll get better after Grandpa's birthday?
Yes, I think it'll get better.
What if it gets better after a year?
A bird is coming to us.
- You're right. - A bird is coming to us.
- Come here. - Goodness.
(A sparrow approaches Ju Seung's family.)
Did he become a bird?
(Did my husband become a bird?)
Goodness.
Gosh, it's nice to be out.
Let's come out more often.
(A Wonderful Day Made Better by Being Together)
The Han River is close by.
(Next story)
(Proved his presence with his unique sense of style)
(A skilled musician who transcends genres)
(Hello.)
(It's been 4 years since I started living alone.)
(Singer DAWN)
(He starts his morning by opening the windows.)
(A 2-story house welcomed by a small yard)
(My house...)
(is almost like a museum.)
(Preserving the original elements...)
(while adding an Eastern aesthetic)
There are many objects inspired by intangible cultural heritage.
(A space filled with items of his taste)
I like placing the items I like nonchalantly.
(DAWN house with Haetnim, his dog)
(He enjoys brunch while sitting on the front porch.)
(Slow)
(He's slower than a sloth.)
(How leisurely and peaceful it is.)
(I have my own pace.)
(Sipping peace today as well)
(Puttering around)
(A meditation continued through the touch of his hands)
(Not dwelling on misfortunes,)
(but simply enjoying the peace of hearing no news)
(What do I do?)
(A peace that's suddenly shaken)
(A Simple Day)
(For the crew members who got hungry after running,)
(the cooking chief gets to work.)
(1st round, cold pork slices)
(That must be really delicious.)
(Cold pork slices...)
(must be delicious.)
(2nd round will be carbs.)
Gosh, that must be delicious.
(Teary-eyed)
(Now we are talking.)
(It's time to become one with a team name.)
(Let's call ourselves this.)
(You're indeed a crew leader.)
(Cheers to us who will run together!)
(The affection they have built for each other through time together)
(I'm always watching others.)
(I can totally see you taking care of us.)
(He feels bad for Kian84 who always blames himself.)
(It's because I became soft-hearted.)
(That's why I want to be with you even more.)
(A Friendship Sweeter than Sweat)